{
    "subject": "resource/WVJS",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/homepage",
    "object": "http://www.owensbororadio.com/pages/14818069.php?",
    "human_readable": "The homepage of WVJS is http://www.owensbororadio.com/pages/14818069.php?",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9572635889053345,
            "question": "Is 'http://www.owensbororadio.com/pages/14818069.php?' a valid URL?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8832593560218811,
            "question": "What is the URL of the WVJS homepage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8490524291992188,
            "question": "What information might be found on the WVJS homepage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8247615694999695,
            "question": "What type of website is likely associated with the WVJS homepage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.816589891910553,
            "question": "Where can you find the WVJS homepage online?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8136200308799744,
            "question": "Is the WVJS homepage hosted by Owensboro Radio?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7870464324951172,
            "question": "Can you access the WVJS homepage with a web browser?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7281100153923035,
            "question": "How might the WVJS homepage be used by its audience?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28422829508781433,
            "question": "What is the purpose of a website homepage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22848345339298248,
            "question": "Does the provided URL lead to a webpage?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The homepage of WVJS is http://www.owensbororadio.com/pages/14818069.php?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6020_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the purpose of a website homepage?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6020_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How might the WVJS homepage be used by its audience?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6020_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you access the WVJS homepage with a web browser?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6020_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6020_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6020_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6020_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6020_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6020_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6020_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6020_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6020_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6020_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6020_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation:\n\nThe query is \"The homepage of WVJS is http://www.owensbororadio.com/pages/14818069.php?\"\n\nAccording to the documents, the correct homepage URL for WVJS is indeed:\n\"The website (URL) for 92.9 WVJS is: http://www.owensbororadio.com/wvjs/\"\n\nSo, the answer is:\n\n{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided documents do not contain any information about the homepage URL for WVJS being `http://www.owensbororadio.com/pages/14818069.php?`. The correct URL given in the documents is `http://www.owensbororadio.com/wvjs/`, not the one specified in the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " Query: The homepage of WVJS is http://www.owensbororadio.com/pages/14818069.php?\nResponse: {'output': 'no'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The correct website URL for 92.9 WVJS was provided in the context information as \"http://www.owensbororadio.com/wvjs/\" and not as \"http://www.owensbororadio.com/pages/14818069.php?\".",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}